[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Are we trying to pull
as many strings as we can
here in the NCIA?
If I were to complete
the retraining,
those groups might have already
come up with a plan against us!
I order you not to dig into
the case any further.
Ma'am Sam, disobeying
Sir Delgado is dangerous.
If that's what it takes,
I'll do it.
One for all. All for one.
Her name is Samantha Jacinto.
The youngest daughter
of the former NLEA chief.
She arrested Victor.
We need to teach her a lesson.
Once I get out of here,
I'll collect you myself.
I'll get you
and your whole family!
We need money.
Isn't Gabo doing everything
he can
to be able to fund his father's
operation?
I'm not coming back here
without any money.
We have a bigger problem.
We'll take care of him.
I was hoping to buy some
jewelry from you for my store.
I'll give you a big discount
today.
I'll meet you at the warehouse.
I really need your help.
Is there a mission
you can give me?
You must take the gold
from Mr. Chan.
I don't care if he dies or not.
Lucas.
Ma.
We're going to Mr. Chan.
I'll take care of him myself.
To make sure that the police
won't get anything out of him
- to use against Victor.
- [DEBORAH SIGHS]
Do you really have
to come along?
Just let your men
do all the work!
Let your son learn how to fight
while Victor is gone.
But there's a lot at stake here!
What if he fails?
What will happen
to our business?
Lucas,
we don't know how long your
brother will be in jail for.
You're the only one
we can count on.
Ma, this is nothing.
I got this!
- Arturo.
- Ma'am.
- Go with them.
- Yes, ma'am.
No need!
Ma,
I'm not a kid anymore.
You no longer need to babysit
your son.
He knows what he's doing.
Lucas, you better make sure
that you'll get rid of Mr. Chan.
Yes, Pa.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
All of you.
Let's move!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CAR HORN HONKS]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
[SEBASTIAN] Thanks.
- [CHAIR CLATTERS]
- [OBJECTS RUSTLING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLICKS]
[SEBASTIAN SIGHS]
Have you calmed down now?
Do you need something?
Sam.
I know it's been a long day.
I tried to give you
some space, but...
But no, I just can't win
against you.
So, please.
Come with me. I even have
a restaurant reservation!
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Now's not really a good time.
Maybe I could... indulge you
next time.
Really? That's a promise!
Yeah, just not right now,
alright? I'm quite busy.
- Excuse me.
- Okay.
It's a promise then. [LAUGHS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SLAMS CLOSE]
Why did you let Lucas leave
without Arturo?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARIANO GROANS]
He's got a lot of men with him.
Don't worry.
Even so. It's still dangerous!
And we cannot afford to risk it
especially with Victor gone!
[CHAIR CLATTERS]
You grew up in this kind
of environment, Deborah.
You know we have to take
risks and fight.
We'll never win
if we always hesitate.
You said it yourself.
We should give Lucas a chance.
Let him do his own thing.
This is the perfect chance
for him to prove himself.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR SLAMS CLOSE]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ARTURO] Ma'am.
Follow Lucas.
Find out what they're up to.
Protect him.
Ma'am, is Sir Mariano
aware of this?
Have you forgotten
where you've come from?
Your father worked for my dad.
I just let Mariano have you.
But no matter what you have
achieved now
you owe it to me and my family.
I know, ma'am.
I'll go after Lucas now.
If anything happens to my son,
you'll be the one
who'll pay for it.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Team, Ma'am Sam is here.
Team, are you ready?
- Yes, ma'am.
We'll capture Mr. Chan.
This time, he won't get away.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Yes, ma'am.
- Let's go.
- Let's!
[RALLOS] Hold it right there!
Where are you going?
Are you guys on a mission?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
We just have somewhere to go.
Can I come?
It's not like I'm an outsider.
You can't come. Stay here.
You'll really leave me behind?
You won't give me something
before you go?
Do you want me
to hit you before I go?
Hey, Ernesto.
You'd better keep quiet!
Zip it!
Good boy.
Let's go.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SEBASTIAN] Rallos?
Sir?
Are you kidding me?
Are there other Rallos here?
Come here.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Sir?
- Where are they?
Why aren't they here?
They're usually here
at this time.
Sir, perhaps an order was given.
Sam was in a hurry earlier.
I feel left out.
She's really giving me
a hard time.
Sir, if Ma'am Sam
is giving you a hard time,
this is just a suggestion,
but why don't you direct your
efforts towards Ma'am Pia.
Do you want me to court her?
- She's not my type.
- [RALLOS] No, sir.
You'll gain Ma'am Pia's trust,
that's when you'll praise
Ma'am Sam to her.
Hmm.
To be honest,
she'll definitely listen to me.
I just need to figure her out.
Sir, just think about all
the brownie points you'll get.
Sam will more
likely say yes
if she finds out
you did that for her.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Pia?
Yes?
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
You know what, Pia,
I just realized that...
you need to have faith
in someone.
Meaning?
Meaning...
You appreciate us agents.
[CHUCKLES] Well, Of course.
My opinion is very
influential in this agency.
I believe in that, Pia.
Pia.
I hope you can
change your mind about Sam.
Let's give her
a second chance.
You know, you'll see her
in a different light.
[SIGHS]
Did Sam ask you to do this?
Are you letting her use you?
No. That's not the case.
Pia.
Lately, I've noticed that Sam
has become more cranky.
But she's eager to solve
the gold smuggling case.
I think she's on to something.
She's really paying attention
to this case.
Paying attention?
Yes,
she's paying attention to it.
I just don't know why
she's not here now.
But usually,
at this time, she's here.
She's really onto
this gold smuggling case.
Let's just let her
prove herself.
You'll be amazed.
Trust me.
[COMICAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hero.
Good job, sir.
Good job.
- [PIA] Sir.
- [DELGADO] Yes?
It feels like your favorite
agent is being nosy.
What do you mean?
I think she's still
on to Tiger's case.
- She disobeyed you.
- I already told her to stop.
I told her she was
hands off on this case.
Well, it seems like
Sam has a point to prove.
Maybe my review
of her was right.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[DOOR CLICKS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, you! Do it faster!
- Double time!
- [CLAPS]
Double time!
Do it faster!
[ENGINE REVS]
Hey, you there!
I want everything out today!
Everything clean today!
Double time! Double time!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR CLICKS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[CASTOR] Team, let's stay here.
Let's wait for them.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[METAL THUDS, CREAKS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [UMALI] Sir.
- [DOMINGO] Yes?
Sir.
I have relayed your message
to Paquito.
Good. I'm expecting
better news tomorrow.
Sir, I was just thinking.
Maybe we could have
other people do the job.
I agree, sir.
They're full of themselves.
They act as if they are
the law.
Especially that Django.
Sir, let's just get rid
of them.
I know other people
who can do the job.
Umali, we've been working with
Paquito for a while now.
I trust their group.
Just ignore their rude behavior.
I mean, they're criminals,
remember?
If you say so, sir.
What matters is that we
get rid of our problem.
Salvador will be gone.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DJANGO] We got a high-paying
job for tomorrow.
That's easy, boss.
Does it involve beating someone
up or stealing?
[SALVADOR ON TV]
After the interview...
We'll rob, threaten him,
and beat him up.
He's our target.
- A mediocre news reporter.
- Someone got hospitalized.
Is it necessary to get
someone hurt?
Boss, he interviewed
Miss Betchay
and did a report
on Mister Rudy.
That's why we need
to teach him a lesson
and keep his mouth shut.
It's a piece of cake, boss.
I know, it's not even
challenging.
I'll do the job without
breaking a sweat.
[LAUGHTER]
You all got this, right?
- [HENCHMAN 1] Of course.
- Django.
- [SALVADOR ON TV] Once again...
I am Salvador "The Vindicator"
Manalo,
supporter of the oppressed.
- Yes, Pa?
- Listen, Django.
Don't underestimate this job.
Whether it involves a big-time
person or not,
you should treat them
equally.
Okay, Pa.
Umali paid us a huge amount
for this job,
so it'd be best that you
do it yourself.
Umali could've hired
other people,
but he entrusted it
to us.
So, we must not get
complacent.
We can't have them
lose their trust in us.
Besides, we need protection
from the police.
Why?
They also need us, so that
makes us even. Right, Pa?
We need them more than
they need us,
so you have to do
the job well.
Do the job that they
want us to do.
Okay, Pa.
Leave it to me.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Rallos.
- Sir.
Where are the others?
Where did they go?
I don't know, sir.
- Tuazon.
- Sir.
Do you know where
the others are?
Sir, I have no idea.
- Yeah, right.
- Do you need anything, sir?
You're obviously lying.
You said that Jacinto
seems focused
on the gold smuggling
case, right?
That's not what I meant,
Ma'am Pia.
What I'm trying to say is that
Sam is worried about it.
That's all.
[WHISPERING] They left to deal
with a gold smuggling case?
Rallos!
Do you know anything
about what they're doing?
N--No, sir.
- I was just thinking...
- [DELGADO] What?
If they went some place,
it's possible they went there.
Where?
This is gross insubordination!
They are acting
without my permission!
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I want everything out
today, okay?
Put all my stocks
in the truck.
- Clear?
- Yes, boss.
[PHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
- Hi, Mr. Chan.
It's Carlota.
Yes. Yes, I remember you.
Beautiful girl, yes.
Yes. I'm here outside
the building.
You come inside.
I'll wait for you here.
[CALL DROPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Good evening, ma'am.
- Good evening.
We have a meeting
with Mr. Chan
to purchase some
jewelry.
Okay. I'll accompany you
to him.
[DELGADO] Rallos, call Limbaga.
Sir, why me?
Why you? Aren't you two close?
[WHISPERING] Call her now.
Really? Me?
[SEBASTIAN] Why aren't
you calling her?
Are you hiding something?
No, sir.
If I knew, I would've joined
them in their mission.
That is, if they are
on a mission.
[PIA] Sir.
I found Mr. Chan's
calling card.
I think this is where
they went.
Sam pursued the case even though
I told her to stop.
I'm not going to let anyone
ignore my orders
here in NCIA!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Alright. Jacinto is in.
Let's just wait
for her go signal.
I have a bad feeling about this.
This place looks dangerous.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mr. Chan.
I'm Carlota.
We talked on the phone.
We're the ones who'll buy
jewelry from you.
Yes, I remember you.
Beautiful girl.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
Sorry, we're doing business here
today. My shop is closed.
It's really hot.
Want some water?
Oh... It's okay.
Wait, you said you're closed.
Why are you closed?
None of your business.
You're very beautiful.
Last time, I didn't
notice since I was busy.
Now I see how pretty you are.
[KAREN CHUCKLES]
Mr. Chan, do you think
I'm beautiful, too?
Oh! Sorry about that. My friend
here is just a big joker.
This is Jessica. She's my
partner in this business.
Mr. Chan.
Sir, is there any way you
could give us a huge discount?
We're buying in bulk anyway.
Beautiful girl, no problem.
- I'll give you a 70% discount.
- Mm.
Uh... Sir, I noticed you have
an attaché case there.
Do you have jewelry inside?
Can we take a look?
It holds gold bars.
Want a gold bar?
I'll give you gold bars
at 70% off, too.
Go on a date with me.
Let's fly to China!
We'll shop
and I will pay for everything!
Carlota, say yes! Think of
how much money we'll make!
Plus, he's practically
giving it away, right?
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, come on.
We came here for business.
We do business, no dates.
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR DOORS OPEN]
[GUNSHOTS]
Who are they?!
[GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
- What's that? What's that?
- Mr. Chan!
Enemies are attacking!
Hey, check everything!
Double check it!
- Reyes, hurry, get inside!
- Let's go!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
[ROPE CINCHING TIGHT]
- [ROPE ZIPPING ALONG LINE]
- [THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLOWS LAND]
- [KICKS LAND]
- [GRUNTS LOUDLY]
- [SLINGSHOT STRETCHING, TWANGS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[GRUNTS, KICK LANDS]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [SLINGSHOT TWANGS]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
[GUNSHOTS CONTINUE]
[GRUNTING LOUDLY]
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[KICKS LAND]
[SLINGSHOT TWANGS]
Spread out! We're wiping out
Mr. Chan's men!
[YELLS] Ah!
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[MEN GROANING IN PAIN]
- [SLINGSHOT TWANGS]
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SLINGSHOT STRETCHING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC SWELLS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
[BODY THUDS]
- [PUNCHES AND KICKS LANDING]
- [GLASS SHATTERING]
Victor's freedom rests
in Lucas's hands.
I'll do whatever it takes
to save my brother!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [PUNCHES AND KICKS LANDING]
[GRUNTING LOUDLY]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GROANS IN PAIN]
- Let's go!
[KICKS LAND, THWACKING]
Will Gabo finally
succeed in his mission?
- Mr. Chan!
- We need our car right now!
Or face a whole
new set of challenges?
Freeze! NCIA! Nobody move!